eagetutor.com 2018-05-22

# Privacy Policy

eAgeTutor.com has prepared this Privacy Statement to specify our commitment to your privacy. We seek to provide you with a secure and confidential online environment, and understand and appreciate that you are concerned about the confidentiality and security of personal information that you submit on the Site. We hope that you will:

  1. Feel comfortable using our Web services;

  2. Feel secure submitting information to us;

  3. Understand that you may contact us with your questions or concerns about privacy on this site.

Before registering with us, we kindly ask that you carefully read this Privacy Statement. Any information that you provide to us shall be governed by the terms contained herein. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Statement at any time. If you have questions or feedback about this statement or any privacy issues concerning eAgeTutor.com, please email us at wecare@eAgeTutor.com.

**Information We Collect**  

At the Site, we ask you to provide personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address, and telephone number. We may also collect demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, school, grade, and interests. If you choose to purchase eAgeTutor.com services, we will ask for additional information, such as your credit card number and billing address. A minor can use the site as a user/nominated user; however, the registration and payment process to any facility at the site should be completed by a parent/guardian or other person who can legally enter into a contract on behalf of the user. Finally, like other Web sites, we use technologies, such as ï¿½cookies,ï¿½ to collect information whenever you visit eAgeTutor.com. We explain our use of these technologies below. Information that we collect from you that does not personally identify you shall not be considered personal.

As you create your username and password, or register an eAgeTutor.com account, you may be asked to provide questions and secret answers, as well as an alternate e-mail address, which we will use to help to verify your identity and to assist in resetting your password. After you have registered, you will be asked to sign in with an assigned username and password. You can use the same username and password to sign in for different facilities available on the Site, as well as those of select eAgeTutor.com partners. By signing in on one e-Age site or service, you may be automatically signed into other e-Age sites and services. 

We may also use technologies, such as cookies and web beacons, to collect information about the pages you view, the links you click and other actions you take on our sites and services. Additionally, we collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses.

If you use or access the Site or any facility, in any manner, our system will record the date and time of your visit, the pages viewed and all the activity done by you. When you receive newsletters, etc. from us, we may use web beacons, customized links or similar technologies to determine whether the e-mail has been opened and which links you click to provide you more focused e-mail communications or other information. We will, at our discretion, store , destroy or use such information, which you hereby agree is not and shall not be considered private or personal, notwithstanding anything to the contrary.

You are able to access and update the personal information that we hold about you at any time. To amend or add personal information, please visit my eAgeTutor once you have logged in.

From time to time the Site may contain links to other websites, including some submitted by third parties. eAgeTutor.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those websites.

**Personal Information Security**  

Your privacy is among our top concerns. We work hard to earn and keep your trust, and so will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes. We will use industry standard protocols and technology to secure any sensitive information that you provide.

Unfortunately, no method of transmitting and storing data can be guaranteed to be totally secure. Accordingly, while we will strive to protect personal information, eAgeTutor cannot fully ensure or warrant its security. Once we receive your private information, we will take reasonable steps to preserve its security on our own system. All information gathered on our Site is stored in limited access facilities.

Should you, at some time, have a User Account, your account information will be password and user ID protected. We recommend that you do not divulge your password or user ID to anyone.

eAgeTutor uses a third-party vendor (paypal.com) to accept payments for eAgeTutor services. Paypal.com is a secure online method of payment, and your information is protected by SSL with an encryption key length of 168 bits (the highest level commercially available). eAgeTutor never receives your financial information such as your bank account number or your credit card information. Your personal information stored by Paypal.com is heavily guarded, both physically and electronically. To further shield your credit card and bank numbers. You can refer to Paypal.com to learn more about how they keep your information and identity safe.

**How We Use Personal Information**

eAgeTutor.com uses the information that we collect for purposes such as providing services to our customers, processing payments, and improving our practices. For instance, we may use the information to contact customers to discuss their interest in our services, and to send information about eAgeTutor.com and its partners. If you would prefer not to be contacted or to receive such information, please e-mail us at [wecare@eagetutor.com](mailto:wecare@eagetutor.com "wecare@eagetutor.com").

We will use or send personal information that we collect from you to other companies or people when: 

  * We will use or send personal information that we collect from you to other companies or people when:
  * We have your consent to share the information;
  * We require it for market or service research purposes, for which we may contact you by e-mail/fax/phone;
  * We need to share your information to provide the facility you have requested;
  * We need to share the information with certain service partners;
  * We have to respond to requests from any government, security, defense, revenue, regulatory or other authority, agency or officer;
  * We send you promotional emails about new products, special offers, or promotions that we think might be of interest to you;
  * We have to share your information in compliance with any legal or Court requirement or procedure, etc, such as the Siteï¿½s Duty to Warn; or
  * We find that your actions on our Site violate the terms of the User Agreement / Terms and Conditions or any of our usage guidelines.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so please check back occasionally. Any information collected after an amended Privacy Policy has been posted on this site, will be subject to that amended Privacy Policy.

**Acceptance of this Privacy Policy**  

You acknowledge and accept that your use of the Site indicates your acceptance of the Site terms and conditions of use and that you understand this Privacy Policy. 

You acknowledge and accept that your use of the Site indicates your acceptance of the Site terms and conditions of use and that you understand this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so please check back occasionally. Any information collected after an amended Privacy Policy has been posted on this site, will be subject to that amended Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions or feedback about this statement or any privacy issues concerning eAgeTutor.com, please send us an email at [wecare@eagetutor.com](mailto:wecare@eagetutor.com "wecare@eagetutor.com").

The safety of our users is of paramount importance to us, please take a moment to review our safety policy.
